Ali Shan Haider Jaffiery



Cell: 0304-5127214

Email: Shanz5127214@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 04/25/1998

Islamabad, Pakistan

SUMMARY

7 months of experience in front-end development knowledge in HTML, CSS, React Js, Redux. I have done different projects in university and made Livestock, Student QR Code websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript. Now working on more projects. 6 months of experience in android apps development. I have made 2 apps using Java language, Fake Call Prank and Best Match.

EXPERIENCE

Android Developer – Internship (March, 2022 – Present)

Hazza Institute and Technology

Fake Call Prank

- I created this app for Android mobile user.
- In this app the end user give input of fake screens by using screenshots.
- Create different modules like (audio call, another call & video call) for end user.

Technologies: XML, JAVA

Best Match

- I created this app for Android mobile user.
- This app is for Best Match makers.
- End user input their names and calculate the percentage of matching. **Technologies:** XML, JAVA

Front-end Development (January, 2022 – July, 2022)

Self-Employed

Student QR Code

- It is an online learning website.
- This website helps the end user for learning online.
- Create different modules for end user like (Lectures, Assignments, Quizzes, Notifications)

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript

Livestock

- The purpose of Livestock is to provide online qurbani animals.
- Pictures and description are mentioned.
- Including the types and prices of the goats and other sacrificial animals.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript

Data Entry Operator (February, 2017 – April, 2017)

National Testing Service (NTS)

- Data Entry of Government employment forms.
- Verification of filled forms.



Data Entry Operator (January, 2019 – March, 2019)

National Consulting for Business & Management Solutions (Pvt) Ltd. (NCBMS)

- Data Entry of Loans forms.
- Supervision of submitted forms .

Lion Forces Academy

• Still working with this academy (online work)

EDUCATION

- BS (Software Engineering) (2022)
- Higher Secondary (ICS) (2016)
- Matriculation (Medical) (2014)

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Reading, Travelling & Sports.